anvari.org 2010-06-20

# Privacy Policy

|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
| 

### Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

### The Information Anvari.org Collects

  1. User Provided Information: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to Anvari.org when choosing to leaving comments on articles, or signing guestbook. 
  2. Cookies Information: When you visit anvari.org, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the site (such as password-protected areas) may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 
  3. Log File Information: When you use anvari.org, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 

### The Way Anvari.org Uses Information

  1. We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major site changes or for customer service purposes). 
  2. We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of anvari.org and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends. 

### When Anvari.org Discloses Information

  1. We do share non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on anvari.org. 
  2. We may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright Law) or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant. 

### 3rd Party Partners

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on anvari.org.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 
  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

### Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information, in which case Anvari.org may not be able to provide certain services to you. Please contact Anvari.org with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, your consent, or your opt-in or opt-out choices using this contact form. 

|   
|  |
